<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bizgrowthh</string>
    <string name="faq1">* What is “Feasibility” and “Viability” of a business?

“Feasibility” is examining the possibility of manufacturing the product or delivering the service.
“Viability” is examining the sustainability of the proposed business activity in the coming years.</string>
    <string name="faq2">* How long does it take Bizgrowth to create a Business Plan?

It takes approximately 4 working days once all documents along with the required information is received.</string>
    <string name="faq3">*  Why should I create a Business Plan and Project Report?

Writing a business plan is an opportunity to carefully think through every step of starting your business and helps in a number of ways including:
* Validating your assumptions and determining the need for your product or service in the market.
* Giving a structure to your idea and saving time and resources in the long run.
* Making projections that give you a good understanding of how your business will operate in the future.</string>
    <string name="faq4">* When can a Business Plan be prepared?

Business Plan can be prepared when you are planning to start a business, so as to understand the ‘Viability’ and ‘Feasibility’ of the proposed business idea. Also, for existing businesses when the entrepreneur is planning to expand the business or while introducing a new line of service or product or while opening a new branch etc.
</string>
    <string-array name="Sector">
        <item>All</item>
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Other than Food</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="businessstage">
        <item>Start</item>
        <item>Manage</item>
        <item>Grow</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="category">
        <item>Legal Compliances</item>
        <item>Business Performance Improvement</item>
        <item>Professional Services</item>
        <item>Marketing</item>
        <item>Consultation</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Countries">
        <item>USA</item>
        <item>Europe</item>
        <item>UK</item>
        <item>Australia</item>
        <item>Korea</item>
        <item>Russia</item>
        <item>Japan</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>Israel</item>
        <item>Qatar</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>